Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - P
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Pumpin' it up, 1983; SR-23001; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          Promo
          Catalog # 4Z9 04981; A-side Matrix # P-4Z9-04981-4-AA
          CBS Associated Records
          New York, New York
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Generator pop; Hydraulic pump, 1983; SR-23002; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23003. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 4Z9 04224; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04224-3-AA
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Generator pop; Hydraulic pump, 1983; SR-23003; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23002. 2 copies.
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Generator pop; Hydraulic pump, 1983; SR-23004; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
        - P-Funk All Stars - Hydraulic pump, 1983; SR-23005; P-Funk All Stars; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          Catalog # H-111; A-side Matrix # H-111-A-T2
          Hump Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Live at the Beverly Theater in Hollywood (disc one), 1990; SR-23006; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23007; SR-23008; SR-23009. Double album; 2 copies.
          Catalog # SEW2 031; A-side Matrix # 008 DMD-6588 A-1
          Westbound Records
          London, United Kingdom
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Live at the Beverly Theater in Hollywood (disc two), 1990; SR-23007; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23006; SR-23008; SR-23009. Double album; 2 copies.
          Catalog # SEW2 031; A-side Matrix # 008 DMD-6588 A-2
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Live at the Beverly Theater in Hollywood (disc one), 1990; SR-23008; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23006; SR-23007; SR-23009. Double album; 2 copies.
        - P. Funk All-Stars - Live at the Beverly Theater in Hollywood (disc two), 1990; SR-23009; P. Funk All-Stars; Clinton, George (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23006; SR-23007; SR-23008. Double album; 2 copies.
        - P4F - P. Machinery; Relax (Medley), 1986; SR-23010; P4F (Box 382)
          Catalog # EMDS 6562; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6562-A
          Emergency Records
        - Paape, Jürgen - So weit wie noch nie, 2003; SR-23011; Paape, Jürgen (Box 382)
          Catalog # 82876 54825 1; A-side Matrix # B385311-01 A1 KR
          Low Spirit Recordings
          Berlin, Germany
        - Pablo - Story of sampling ep, 2001; SR-23012; Pablo (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23013. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RH 003; A-side Matrix # RH-003-172
          Red Hook Recordings
          Glasgow, Scotland
        - Pablo - Story of sampling ep, 2001; SR-23013; Pablo (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23012. 2 copies.
        - Pablo, Augustus - East of the river Nile, 1978; SR-23014; Pablo, Augustus (Box 382)
          Catalog # DSR 7108; A-side Matrix # DSR 7108-A D.T.
          Message
          Jamaica
        - Pablo, Petey - I told y'all, 2002; SR-23015; Pablo, Petey; Timbaland (Box 382)
          Catalog # 01241-40006-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-40006-1 A
          Jive
        - Pablo, Petey - Freek-a-leek, 2004; SR-23016; Pablo, Petey (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23017. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 82876-58745-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-58745-1 A
        - Pablo, Petey - Freek-a-leek, 2004; SR-23017; Pablo, Petey (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23016. 2 copies.
        - Pablo, Petey - Raise up, 2001; SR-23018; Pablo, Petey; Timbaland (Box 382)
          Catalog # 01241-42876-1R; A-side Matrix # 01241-42876-1RA
        - Pablo, Petey - Give it up, 2005; SR-23019; Pablo, Petey; Lil' Jon (Box 382)
          Catalog # 82876-75482-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-75482-1 A
        - Pablo, Petey - Give it up, 2005; SR-23020; Pablo, Petey; Lil' Jon (Box 382)
        - Pablo, Petey - Give it up, 2005; SR-23021; Pablo, Petey; Lil' Jon (Box 382)
        - Sticky - Paccman, 2002; SR-23022; Sticky (Box 382)
          Catalog # JKSC 023; A-side Matrix # JKSC 023 AA
          Social Circles
          United Kingdom
        - Pace Won - Secret; Bring it out of me, 2000; SR-23023; Pace Won; Pacewon (Box 382)
          Catalog # PW0202; A-side Matrix # PW0202-A
          Ruffwax Records
          United States
        - Pace Won - I declare war; Step up, 1999; SR-23024; Pace Won; Pacewon (Box 382)
          Catalog # CAS 41798; A-side Matrix # XSS-41798A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Pacheco - El maestro, 1975; SR-23025; Pacheco; Casanova, Hector (Box 382)
          Catalog # SLP 00485; A-side Matrix # SLP-00485-A
          Fania Records
        - Pacific Blue - Argentina forever; You gotta dance, 1978; SR-23026; Pacific Blue (Box 382)
          Catalog # PRL-D 153; A-side Matrix # PRLD 153A
          Prelude Records
        - Pacific Orchestra - Infinity ship, 1984; SR-23028; Pacific Orchestra (Box 382)
          Catalog # GZPZ 12001; A-side Matrix # GZPZ-12001-A
          GZPZ Records
          Washington D.C.
        - Pacino, Chris - Drop the beat, 1991; SR-23029; Pacino, Chris (Box 382)
          Catalog # DW 1923; A-side Matrix # DW 1923-SIDE A
          Dance and Waves
          Italy
        - Packman - I'm the packman (eat everything I can), 1982; SR-23030; Packman (Box 382)
          Catalog # EN-1163; A-side Matrix # EN-1163
          Enjoy Records
        - Paco and Flaco - He's here, 1980; SR-23031; Paco and Flaco; Coco (Box 382)
          Catalog # TKD-446; A-side Matrix # TKD-446-A-AM
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Padilla, Sonny, Jr. - It's your body, 1985; SR-23032; Padilla, Sonny, Jr. (Box 382)
          Catalog # UNO-585-12; A-side Matrix # UNO-585-12A
          Uno Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Pagan, Bruni - Follow me, 1982; SR-23035; Pagan, Bruni (Box 382)
          Catalog # TAS-2803; A-side Matrix # TAS-2803-E-A
        - Págan, Bruni - Fantasy, 1979; SR-23036; Págan, Bruni (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23037. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS-11423; A-side Matrix # ASS-11423-A-SP-1
          Elektra
        - Págan, Bruni - Fantasy, 1979; SR-23037; Págan, Bruni (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23036. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # AS-11423; A-side Matrix # ASS-11423-A-SP 1-2
        - Pagan, Ralfi - With love, 1992; SR-23038; Pagan, Ralfi (Box 382)
          Catalog # 397; A-side Matrix # L-16188
          Marketing West
          Los Angeles, California
        - Pagano, John - Let's get to it, 1992; SR-23039; Pagano, John; Mundy, Nick (Box 382)
          Catalog # MCA8P 1657; A-side Matrix # MCA 11251 FDS-2
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Page, Tommy - Turning me on (remix), 1988; SR-23040; Page, Tommy (Box 382)
          Catalog # PRO-A-3260; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-3260 SH1
          Sire
        - Paige, Raiana - Open up your heart, 1988; SR-23041; Paige, Raiana (Box 382)
          Catalog # SLX-40140; A-side Matrix # SLX-40140X-RE1
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Pointe, An - Magé et vacciné; Zouk.Gua.Ma.Gui, 1988; SR-23042; Pointe, An; Pajot, Eugène (Box 382)
          Catalog # 15.13; A-side Matrix # No 1513A
          France
        - Palmer, Jeree - Late night surrender, 1979; SR-23043; Palmer, Jeree (Box 382)
          Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # PC 126; A-side Matrix # PC 126A
          Reflection Records
        - Palmer, Jeree - Baby how long; Love child, 1980; SR-23044; Palmer, Jeree (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23045. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CBL-132; A-side Matrix # CBL-132-A
        - Palmer, Jeree - Baby how long; Love child, 1980; SR-23045; Palmer, Jeree (Box 382)
          In same jacket as # SR-23044. 2 copies.
        - Palmer, Robert - Hyperactive, 1985; SR-23046; Palmer, Robert (Box 382)
          Catalog # PR 879; A-side Matrix # STPR-48937-1
          Island Records
        - Palmer, Robert - Pride, 1983; SR-23047; Palmer, Robert (Box 382)
          Catalog # DMD 678; A-side Matrix # STDM-45285-1
        - Palmer, Robert - Looking for clues, 1980; SR-23048; Palmer, Robert (Box 382)
          Catalog # PRO-A-922; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 922 A1 B-15418
        - Palmer, Robert - You are in my system, 1983; SR-23049; Palmer, Robert (Box 382)
          Catalog # DMD 635; A-side Matrix # STDM 44708-1
        - Palmer, Robert - Riptide, 1985; SR-23050; Palmer, Robert (Box 382)
          Catalog # 90471-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-855 795-D 1-3
        - Palmer, Tristan - Take my hand, 1982; SR-23051; Palmer, Tristan (Box 382)
          Catalog # A-2; A-side Matrix # A-1 YOGIS PRODUCT 82 (A-2-A)
          A1 Records
        - Palmieri, Eddie - Recorded live at Sing Sing, 1972; SR-23052; Palmieri, Eddie; Harlem River Drive (Box 382)
          Catalog # CLP-1303; A-side Matrix # TCLP-1303-A-1A A2 E
          Tico Records
        - Palmieri, Eddie - Gold 1973-1976, 1976; SR-23053; Palmieri, Eddie (Box 382)
          Catalog # CLP 133; A-side Matrix # CLP 133A BGST
          Coco Records
        - Palmieri, Eddie - The history of Eddie Palmieri, 1975; SR-23054; Palmieri, Eddie; Quintana, Ismael (Box 382)
          Catalog # TSLP-1403; A-side Matrix # TSLP-1403-A
        - Pamplemousse - Sweet magic, 1978; SR-23055; Pamplemousse (Box 382)
          Catalog # AVI-6053; A-side Matrix # 098-6053-A
          AVI Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Pan Assembly - So hot so sweet, 1987; SR-23056; Pan Assembly (Box 383)
          Catalog # HVLP005; A-side Matrix # C006-87-A
          Carotte
          Trinidad & Tobago
        - Panaché (Just Brothers) - Sweet music, 1979; SR-23057; Panaché (Just Brothers) (Box 383)
          Catalog # R 4000; A-side Matrix # R 4000A
          Rota Enterprises, LTD
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Panaghi, Chris "The Greek" - Funky, 1997; SR-23058; Panaghi, Chris "The Greek" (Box 383)
          Catalog # ZYX 66074-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX 66074-12 A
          ZYX Music
          Germany
        - Pandy, Darryl - I love music, 1990; SR-23059; Pandy, Darryl (Box 383)
          Catalog # 0-21599; A-side Matrix # 0-21599-A SR1
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - Panjabi MC - The album (disc one), 2003; SR-23060; Panjabi MC (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23061. Double album.
          Catalog # DHARMALP1; A-side Matrix # DHARMALP1A-1-1
          Superstar Recordings
        - Panjabi MC - The album (disc two), 2003; SR-23061; Panjabi MC (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23060. Double album.
          Catalog # DHARMALP1; A-side Matrix # DHARMALP1C-1-1
        - Panjabi MC - Beware of the boys (mundian to bach ke), 2003; SR-23062; Panjabi MC (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23063. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SEQ 8011; A-side Matrix # SEQ-8011-A
          Sequence Records
        - Panjabi MC - Beware of the boys (mundian to bach ke), 2003; SR-23063; Panjabi MC (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23062. 2 copies.
        - Panjabi MC - Beware of the boys (mundian to bach ke) - the dance remixes, 2003; SR-23064; Panjabi MC (Box 383)
          Catalog # UL 1163-6; A-side Matrix # UL-1163-A
          Ultra Records
        - Catelli Trinidad All Stars - Panorama alive Carnival fever: volume 1, 1980; SR-23065; Catelli Trinidad All Stars; Gerizim Angel Harps; Our Boys (Box 383)
          Catalog # C00787; A-side Matrix # C00787 A
        - Papa Chuk - The Badlands, 1994; SR-23066; Papa Chuk (Box 383)
          Catalog # E1-28546; A-side Matrix # E1-28546-A
          Pendulum Records
        - Papa Chuk - The Badlands, 1994; SR-23067; Papa Chuk (Box 383)
        - Papa Chuk - Funky science; Texas roughneck, 1992; SR-23068; Papa Chuk (Box 383)
          Catalog # 0-66414; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66414-A-1
        - Papa Reu - Represent, 2005; SR-23069; Papa Reu; Lil' Flip; Bigga Boss (Box 383)
          Catalog # SURDJ-85691-1; A-side Matrix # SURDJ 85691-1 A
          Sanctuary Urban
        - Papa Reu - Represent, 2005; SR-23110; Papa Reu; Lil' Flip; Bigga Boss (Box 383)
        - Papa Ricky - Lu sole mio, 1992; SR-23070; Papa Ricky (Box 383)
          Catalog # CVX 003; A-side Matrix # CVX 003 A
          Century Vox Records
          Ancona, Italy
        - Papa San - Style & fashion, 1989; SR-23071; Papa San (Box 383)
          Catalog # PW 7410; A-side Matrix # PW 7410 A
          Pow Wow Records
        - Papa San - Dance hall good to we, 1990; SR-23072; Papa San (Box 383)
          Catalog # PW 459; A-side Matrix # PW-459 A
        - Papa Wemba - Siku ya mungu, 1987; SR-23073; Papa Wemba (Box 383)
          Catalog # NS 5504; A-side Matrix # CEL 5504 A
          Nova Scratch
          Paris, France
        - Paperboy - Bumpin' (adaptation of humpin'), 1993; SR-23074; Paperboy (Box 383)
          Catalog # 162-350-021-1; A-side Matrix # 162-350-021-1 AS/HB
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - PaperView - Krunkin'; Catch u in da hood, 2005; SR-23075; PaperView (Box 383)
          Catalog # SOG-001; A-side Matrix # SOG-001 A RE1
          S.O.G. Entertainment
          Orlando, Florida
        - Papp, Julius - The soul'd out project, 1996; SR-23076; Papp, Julius (Box 383)
          Catalog # JC 2006; A-side Matrix # JC-2006 A
          Jazz Club
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Paradis, Vanessa - Joe le taxi, 1988; SR-23077; Paradis, Vanessa (Box 383)
          Catalog # POSPX 902; A-side Matrix # POSPX 902 A
          Polydor
        - Paradise Express - You set me on fire; We are one, 1979; SR-23078; Paradise Express (Box 383)
          Catalog # D-150; A-side Matrix # D-150A-1A
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - Parental Advisory - Like we do, 1998; SR-23079; Parental Advisory (Box 383)
          Catalog # PRO-A-5051; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-5051-DRM-A-GL1
          DreamWorks Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Parental Advisory - Just like that; Sundown, 2000; SR-23080; Parental Advisory (Box 383)
          Catalog # DRMR-13606-1; A-side Matrix # DRMR-13606-1 A
        - Parental Advisory - Maniac, 1993; SR-23081; Parental Advisory (Box 383)
          Catalog # MCA8P 2756; A-side Matrix # MCA-11791-HF2
          Santa Monica, California
        - Parental Advisory - Maniac, 1993; SR-23082; Parental Advisory (Box 383)
        - Parental Advisory - Maniac, 1993; SR-23083; Parental Advisory (Box 383)
        - Paris - The devil made me do it, 1990; SR-23084; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # TB-962; A-side Matrix # TB 962-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Paris - The days of old, 1992; SR-23085; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SX-69-001; A-side Matrix # SX-69-001-A
          Scarface Records
          Oakland, California
        - Paris - Fair weather friendz, 1998; SR-23086; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # WH-0001; A-side Matrix # WH 0001-A
          Unleashed Records
          Danville, California
        - Paris - Guerrilla funk, 1994; SR-23087; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SPRO 50821; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50821-A
          Priority Records
        - Paris - One time fo' ya mind, 1994; SR-23088; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SPRO 50840; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50840-A
        - Paris - Guerrilla funk, 1994; SR-23089; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SPRO 50818; A-side Matrix # PVL-53169-A
        - Paris - FNB; Evil, 2003; SR-23090; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # GFS-100-1; A-side Matrix # GAP3100-1A
          Guerrilla Funk Recordings
        - Paris - The hate that hate made, 1991; SR-23091; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # TB-967; A-side Matrix # TB-967 A
        - Paris - Outta my life; Bring it to ya, 1995; SR-23092; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SPRO 50837; A-side Matrix # PVL-53178-A
        - Paris - Assata's song, 1993; SR-23093; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # SCR07-102-1; A-side Matrix # SCR07-102-1-A
        - Paris - FNB; Evil, 2003; SR-23094; Paris (Box 383)
        - Paris - The devil made me do it, 1990; SR-23095; Paris (Box 383)
        - Paris - The devil made me do it, 1990; SR-23096; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # TB 1030; A-side Matrix # TB 1030-A
        - Paris - FNB; Evil, 2003; SR-23097; Paris (Box 383)
        - Paris - Break the grip of shame, 1989; SR-23098; Paris (Box 383)
          Catalog # TB 950; A-side Matrix # TB 950-A
        - Paris, Mica - So good, 1988; SR-23099; Paris, Mica (Box 383)
          Catalog # 90970-1; A-side Matrix # ST 1L 887235 C DMM
        - Park, Gidea - Seasons of gold; Lolita, 1981; SR-23100; Park, Gidea (Box 383)
          Catalog # PRO-7003; A-side Matrix # PRO-7003A-1
          Profile Records
        - Parker, Andrea - Melodious thunk, 1996; SR-23101; Parker, Andrea (Box 383)
          Catalog # MW 040; A-side Matrix # MW0 40A DJ
          Mo Wax
        - Parker, Cecil - What is it, 1981; SR-23102; Parker, Cecil (Box 383)
          Catalog # AS 954; A-side Matrix # AS 954AS-1A
          WMOT Records
        - Parker, Kenny - Make it bounce; Uptown, 1999; SR-23103; Parker, Kenny; Ajax; Kim, Cutty (Box 383)
          Catalog # GFM 002; A-side Matrix # GFME-002-A
          G.F.M. Entertainment
        - Parker, Luna - Tes états d'âme... Eric, 1986; SR-23104; Parker, Luna (Box 383)
          Catalog # 883 971-1; A-side Matrix # 883 971-1 A
          Barclay
        - Parker, Maceo - Keep your soul together, 1993; SR-23105; Parker, Maceo; Cole, Russell D.; Don Abi (Box 383)
          Catalog # MM1036; A-side Matrix # MM-1036-A2
          Minor Music
          Blaustein, Germany
        - Parker, Maceo - Let 'em out, 1990; SR-23106; Parker, Maceo (Box 383)
          Catalog # PR 515-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-515-0-ASP
          4th & Broadway
        - Maceo and All the King's Men - Doing their own thing, 1970; SR-23107; Maceo and All the King's Men; Parker, Maceo (Box 383)
          Catalog # HOUSE OF FOX 001; A-side Matrix # 3972-HOFLP1-1(A) S-45706
          House Of The Fox
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Maceo - For all the king's men, 1990; SR-23108; Maceo; Parker, Maceo (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23109. Different discs.
          Catalog # 444 027-1; A-side Matrix # 162-444-027-1-A-SP
        - Maceo - Let 'em out, 1990; SR-23109; Maceo; Parker, Maceo (Box 383)
          In same jacket as # SR-23108. Different discs. Promo
        - Parker, Paul - One look (one look was enough), 1987; SR-23111; Parker, Paul (Box 384)
          Catalog # TGR 1011; A-side Matrix # TGR 1011 A
          Dice Records
        - Parker, Paul - Right on target; Pushin too hard, 1982; SR-23112; Parker, Paul (Box 384)
          Catalog # MT101; A-side Matrix # MT-101-A
          Megatone Records
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - The other woman, 1982; SR-23113; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Catalog # SP-128; A-side Matrix # SP 128-SA